Narrator: A
A: John is Richard’s grandfather.
Narrator: 8
A: Jennifer is Richard’s grandmother.
Narrator: 2
A: Carol is Richard’s mother.
Narrator: 1
A: Gary is Richard’s father.
Narrator: 9
A: Sue is Richard’s aunt.
Narrator: 10
A: Nick is Richard’s uncle.
Narrator: 4
A: Kate is Richard’s sister.
Narrator: 3
A: Steven is Richard’s brother.
Narrator: 13
A: Hugh is Richard’s cousin.
A: Sarah is Richard’s cousin.
Narrator: 14
A: Emma is Richard’s wife.
Narrator: 5
A: Chloe is Richard’s daughter.
Narrator: 6
A: Jake is Richard’s son.
Narrator: 12
A: Ruby is Richard’s niece.
Narrator: 11
A: Oliver is Richard’s nephew.
Narrator: B
B: my father and my mother
my parents
Narrator: 2
B: my wife’s mother and father
my parents-in-law
Narrator: 3
B: my grandfather and my grandmother
my grandparents
Narrator: 4
B: my son and my daughter
my children
Narrator: 5
B: a husband and wife
a couple